

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

# YAZMIN PEDRAZA ORTIZ



www.yazminpedraza.com



github.com/YazminPedraza



yazminpedraza.it@gmail.com



Mexico City

#### **TECNOLOGIES**

- Git y GitHub
- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Sass
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Yarn / NPM

## **SKILLS**

- Time management
- Commitment
- Detail oriented
- Team player
- Sharing knowledge
- Lifelong learning

### **CERTIFICATES**

**Scrum Fundamentals Certified**Scrum Study | January 2019

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Instituto Politecnico Nacional | 2014 - 2018

### **LANGUAGES**

**English - B2 level** (Upper-intermediate by CEF)

# **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

I am a passionate front-end developer with over two years of professional experience in web development and one year of hands-on experience in React.js. I am looking to continue growing as a front-end developer and eventually perform as a full-stack.

# **CAREER SUMMARY**

## Front - end developer

TGC Internet Group | September 2019 - present

- Front-end development of the contactaabogado.com platform.
- Working with React.js, Sass, Material-UI, Redux, React Router, moment.js, and react-google-charts.

#### **IT Trainee**

Tata Consultancy Services | February - September 2019

- Ab Initio training (ETL tool).
- Participation in additional courses in Python, JavaScript, Agile, SCRUM and data science.

## Web develoment internship

UbicTrans | October - November 2018

• I took part in the development of a mobility app that used the Google Maps API for tracking and geolocalization.

## Web development volunteer

Instituto Politecnico Nacional | November 2017 - Jun 2018

- Website optimization using PageSpeed Insights.
- Front-end and back-end programming of forms and tables using JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX and PHP.
- Use of the Google Maps API.